# DANIEL SANCHO JARA

## Full Stack Web Developer

#### CONTACT

- d.sancho.23@hotmail.com
  - +34 644743458 🤳
  - Valencia, Spain 👂
    - LinkedIn in
      - Github (
- https://dani-sancho.github.io/

#### **EDUCATION**

Web Application Development Professional Training IES Conselleria 2017 - 2018

Valencia, Spain

Networks and Microcomputer Systems Medium Training IES Conselleria 2015 - 2016 Valencia, Spain

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

#### Languajes

HTML CSS

SCSS

JavaScript

PHP

MySQL + MariaDB

Gi

TypeScript

**Libraries and Standards** 

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am passionate about web design, Full Stack Web developer, high skilled Front-End experience and a nice level of database management & PHP Back-End, with proven experience at Infortisa S.L. developing and maintaining Web applications with documented and reusable code. I love to learn and develop new things, and I am always willing to face new challenges and difficulties, including learning new frameworks or structures. In general, most Front-Ends tend to follow a pattern, adopting the styles, templates and tools already established and I, in addition to that, am the one who defines all that structure, thus being able to create templates from scratch, or adapt to an already established design.

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

My objective is to bring both my potential and my knowledge to a company that helps me grow both personally and professionally.

 These last three years I have been working from home in a hybrid way, and I consider that it is the way I feel most motivated and in which I can best exploit my capacity, so I would be delighted to take on a hybrid or telecommuting position.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Developer

INFORTISA S.L.

lune 2018 - current / Valencia

- Development & design of Responsive Web application
- Web Application maintenance
- Database management
- Creating and maintaining Ajax with PHP
- Creating and maintaining models and controllers with PHP
- Optimization, explanation and reusability of the code
- Task management through Freedcamp or Youtrack, with Kanban methodology
- Version control with Git

jQuery JWT MVC Smarty Youtrack, Freedcamp

#### Frameworks

Ionic (Cordova, Capacitor, WebApp)

Angular

Custom MVC with .htaccess and
redirection to controllers

#### **Operative Systems**

Windows (7, 8, 10) Linux (Ubuntu)  Guided, instructed and helped in a teleworking environment to 8 Junior programmers and 1 Intermediate programmer incorporated into the Development team, both in Front-End and Back-End methodologies. In the development, a series of 10 practical exercises were designed so that they could gain practice with our working metodology.

### Web Development Coordinator

INFORTISA S.L.

January 2021 - December 2021 / Valencia

• Project leader and team coordinator, with 3 co-workers under my lead.

## Mobile Development with Angular & Ionic

INFORTISA S.L.

February 2021 - June 2021 / Valencia

- Development and design of native android application from scratch with Cordova
- Documented operation and code of the application.